virtuemarttemplates.net 2016-11-21

# Privacy And Cookies Policy

At Virtuemart Templates website we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors and customers.

This Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site or use the services we provide at the website.

### This policy also outlines how we use cookies at this website

#### Information That We Collect

In order to operate, maintain and provide the services we offer at this website we may collect and process the following data about you

  1. Information about your use of our site including details of your visits such as pages viewed and the resources that you access. Such information includes traffic data, location data and other communication data.
  2. Information provided voluntarily by you. For example, when you register for information or make a purchase at the website.
  3. Information that you provide when you communicate with us by any means.

### Use of Cookies

Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a visitor.

We may use cookies where appropriate to gather information about your computer in order to assist us in improving our website.

We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie.

Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer and stored on the computer’s hard drive.

Such information will not identify you personally; it is statistical data which does not identify any personal details whatsoever.

You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if you wish. This can be done within the “settings” section of your computer.

### Use of Your Information

We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you.

In addition to this we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:

  1. To provide information to you that you request from us relating to our products or services we offer at the website.
  2. To inform you of any changes to our website, services or products we offer at the website.

We will never share your details to third parties

### Storing Your Personal Data

In operating our website it may become necessary to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the European Union for processing and storing.

By providing your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing. We do our upmost to ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to make sure that your data is stored securely.

Unfortunately the sending of information via the internet is not totally secure and on occasion such information can be intercepted. We cannot guarantee the security of data that you choose to send us electronically, sending such information is entirely at your own risk.

### Disclosing Your Information

We will not disclose your personal information to any other party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below

  1. In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer.
  2. Where we are legally required by law to disclose your personal information.
  3. To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.

### Third Party Links

On occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide a link it does not mean that we endorse or approve that site’s policy towards visitor privacy. You should review their privacy policy before sending them any personal data.

### Access to Information

In accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 you have the right to access any information that we hold relating to you. If you require access to this information please contact us at the website.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding the privacy and cookies policy outlined in this document please contact us at the website.
